iwowwe.com 2014-12-01

# iWowWe- Video Email, Video Conference and Video Broadcast

Updated and effective January 1, 2011

##### Privacy Statement

Thank you for visiting the iWowWe web site ("Site"). We appreciate the opportunity to interact with you on the Internet and are committed to protecting and safeguarding your privacy. The purpose of this Privacy Statement is to inform you about the types of information we might collect from you when you visit our Site, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct that information.

##### What Information We Collect and How We Use It

Any information we collect on our Site generally falls into the following three categories: 

  * Personally Identifiable Information
  * Secure Information
  * Aggregate Usage Information

Personally Identifiable Information: This refers to information that provides detail about you as a person. In general, you can visit our Site without telling us who you are or revealing any Personally Identifiable Information. You may, however, voluntarily provide Personally Identifiable Information (such as name, e-mail address, and phone number) for us to contact you, including via e-mail, to respond to your comments or inquiries. In such event, we might maintain a record of your contact, including such Personally Identifiable Information. We use this information to provide better service in the event you contact us again.

Secure Information: This refers to information that is generally used for identity theft (e.g., credit card information, social security number, etc.). Secure Information is a subset of Personally Identifiable Information that receives a higher level of protection in our system through specialized encryption.

Aggregate Usage Information: This refers to information that does not by itself identify you as a specific individual. Such information would include the Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") of the Web site that referred you to our Site, your Internet Protocol ("IP") address (a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you surf the Web), your operating system and browser type, and any search terms that you enter on our Site. Our Web server aggregates this information in order to monitor the level of activity on our Site, evaluate its effectiveness, and improve the content of our Site in order to make your visit an easy and enjoyable experience. We may collect, compile, store, publish, promote, report, or otherwise disclose or use any Aggregate Usage Information, provided that, such information does not personally identify you. We do not correlate any Personally Identifiable Information with the Aggregate Usage Information that we collect on our Site. If we do correlate any Aggregate Usage Information to you; it will be protected like any other Personally Identifiable Information under this Privacy Statement.

iWowWe may seek Personally Identifiable Information from Members, through its private Site, to provide you with a service, place an order, or fulfill a request. We will never discuss Secure Information with anyone but the member providing the information. Sharing Your Information

##### Sharing Your Information

Except as disclosed in this Privacy Statement, we do not sell, trade, rent, or otherwise retransmit any Personally Identifiable Information we collect online unless we have your permission. Any Personally Identifiable Information you provide to us will be stored in our databases in the United States.

We may share Personally Identifiable Information you provide online with other iWowWe-related entities and/or trusted business partners with whom we collaborate on our Site functions and activities, as well as those that provide services to our Site. Where we engage non-affiliated third-party agents or contractors for these purposes, we will require them to also protect the confidentiality and integrity of your Personally Identifiable Information and observe the intent of this Privacy Statement.

From time to time, we may be required to provide Personally Identifiable Information in response to court order, subpoena, or government investigation. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful. We may release Personally Identifiable Information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply our Terms of Use or to protect the rights, property, and safety of others and ourselves.

iWowWe or its related entities could merge with or be acquired by another business entity, or its respective assets could be acquired. Should such a merger or acquisition occur, you should expect that we would share some or all of your Personally Identifiable Information to companies serving you and other users of our Site in continuing to provide the services of our Site.

##### Your Choices

Your permission is always secured first. We will not use or share the Personally Identifiable Information collected on our Site in ways unrelated to the purpose for which you provided the information, including those described above, without providing you a choice whether to permit any such unrelated uses.

##### Accessing and Correcting Your Information

We take reasonable measures to ensure that any Personally Identifiable Information we collect on our Site is accurate, current, complete, and reliable for its intended use. If you wish to update or otherwise correct Personally Identifiable Information you have provided to us through our public Site, you may contact us as described in the "Contact Us" section, below. iWowWe Users may modify their own Personally Identifiable Information directly through our Virtual Office private Site.

##### Protecting Your Information

We acknowledge your trust and are committed to take reasonable steps to protect Personally Identifiable Information you provide online from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access. We employ physical, electronic, cryptographic, and managerial processes to safeguard and secure your information.

##### Use of Cookies on This Site

A "cookie" is a small data file transferred to your computer's hard drive that allows a Web site to respond to you as an individual, gathering and remembering information about your preferences in order to tailor its operation to your needs, likes and dislikes.

Overall, cookies are safe, as they only identify your computer to customize your Web experience. Accepting a cookie does not provide access to your computer or any Personally Identifiable Information about you, other than the information you chose to share. Other servers cannot read them, nor can they be used to deliver a virus.

Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually adjust yours (Microsoft Internet Explorer, Netscape Navigator, Google Chrome, or Mozilla Firefox) to notify you of cookie placement requests, refuse certain cookies, or decline cookies completely.

Our Site does place cookies to your computer's hard drive to enhance your experience when visiting our Site.

##### Use of Active-X and Java Applets on This Site

Active-X programs and Java applets are executable programs transferred to your computer's hard drive that cause your computer to perform functions in connection with your visit to a Web site.

Our Site does not transfer any Active-X programs or Java applets to your computer's hard drive.

##### Use of Third-Party Media and Research Companies

Our Site does not run non-affiliated third-party ads, nor do we use third-party media and research companies to place ads for us on other parties' Web sites.

##### Links to Other Web Sites

Links to third-party Web sites may be provided solely for your information and convenience. If you use these links, you will leave our Site. This Privacy Statement does not cover the information practices of those Web sites linked to our Site, nor do we control their content or privacy policies.

iWowWe cannot be liable for any information obtained by outside parties from your use of such links. We cannot guarantee absolute privacy from any hypertext links on our website leading to other websites. We encourage that you be careful providing information to any third parties other than iWowWe. We suggest that you carefully review the privacy policies of each site you visit.

##### Children's Privacy Protection

We take special care to protect the privacy needs of children and encourage parents to be an active participant in their child's online activities.

Our public Site does not target and is not intended for children under the age of 18, and we will not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from them. If we discover personal data from a child through our public Site, we will eliminate that data.

Some Personally Identifiable Information is collected in our private, Members Only, site for accounts (regardless of age) to be able to use the site.

##### Changes to This Statement

Any updates or changes to the terms of this Privacy Statement will be posted here on our Site and the date of the newest version posted just under the title above. Please check back frequently, especially before you submit any Personally Identifiable Information at our site, to see if this Privacy Statement has changed.

By using our Site, you acknowledge acceptance of this Privacy Statement in effect at that time of use. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please discontinue your use of our Site.

##### Email Sent by iWowWe

Email addresses stored in member's address books are wholly owned by the member. iWowWe does not send any email to members' address book contacts except when reviewing the status of "hard bounce" addresses that are reported to be again functional.

iWowWe members are required to accept transactional and product information email from iWowWe as a condition of subscription. This is specified in the Service Agreement during your first logon. You may "opt-out" by cancelling your iWowWe subscription and terminating your relationship with iWowWe by Contacting Customer Support at Support@VideoControlPanel.net.

##### Contact Us

If you have any concerns about our use of your information or about this Privacy Statement, please contact us using the Contact us link on our Site.

We will make every reasonable effort to address your concerns and remedy any problems you bring to our attention.
